Your percentage is very good.  Everything is okay,
but your smile isn't real.  I think it's a
fake smile.  No, sir, you're
laughing well.
No no no no, what do you say, Yashwant garu?
Yes, that's right. Thousands of people will work under you tomorrow
.
Not under that.
That's why you should laugh heartily.
[Laughter] No matter what you say,
Srikanth, that smile is
not fake.
What kind of smile is that? The man is fake.
How did you get that smile on your face, sir?
Do you know what it's like to be a middle-aged boy? You
can do whatever you want, but you do
n't have the support of your family.  Let's marry the girl we like,
but we won't be able to support her.   They
say that we should cry to ease the pain, but you shouldn't cry like a Mogadivi.   If we want to
hide the same pain in our hearts and do
things we don't like for the people we love,
this is called a fake smell.
When else, sir, will we laugh and live?
This is what they feel more than me, the
Tingar Nail Ponies, this is what they feel like
working out.
This guy is working so hard, sir,
calm down, sir, calm down, enough with him, fake,
I'm fake, calm down, sir, calm down, sir, will you
give me a job, sir, you
taught us how to laugh at you, right?
[Laughter] Are you related?